Shlomi Nugarker

Full Stack / Frontend Developer

Phone: 052-952-67-62

Email: Shlomin1231@gmail.com

GitHub:

https://github.com/shlomiNugarker

Summary

Full-Stack / Frontend Web Developer specializing in advanced frameworks, including VueJS, NodeJS, and MongoDB.

Graduate of the Coding Academy - an intensive full-stack development bootcamp. Passionate about technology, striving to learn and extend my knowledge, and a great team player.

Check out my latest project: https://fast-eyrie-76140.herokuapp.com/

Tech Skills

- MVC Frameworks, Single page apps, and PWA using Vue.js.
- Server-side programming, APIs, and REST with Node.JS.
- MongoDB.
- HTML5, CSS3 and SASS.
- Modern JavaScript (ES6) including OOP.
- Vuex.

Experience

A security officer at Google Tel-Aviv - 2018-2021.

A security officer at Israel Postal Company - 2017-2018.

Work at Plasson Industries -2014.

A fighter at Combat Engineering Corps – 2010 - 2013.

Education

2022: Graduate of the Coding Academy Full-Stack Bootcamp.